bro where the [ __ ] you at turn on the
Goddamn lights I can't see a thing I
knew we shouldn't have come to this
stupid abandoned building it's dark as
[ __ ] they what's this Oh a candle just
what we need
there now we can see a pro where did you
go
this isn't funny bro come on out you
better not be off wandering around by
yourself if you get hurt uncle Chuck's
gonna beat your ass
weird he's not responding I better go
look for him but how do I get out that
looks like an air vent up there if I
just had a screwdriver I could climb
through that is to say if my big fat ass
isn't too big for its tiny opening
if only I had some lubricant to make my
butt oh nice
wet and slippery I could slip right on
through luckily I always carry some
butter with me
um oh yeah that's the stuff right there
that sound someone's trying to break in
I'm warning you I'm the lover of Bart
Levy the richest men on earth if you
knew what's good for you you'd stay the
[ __ ] away from me
it's quiet I wonder if you left little
[ __ ] wait what is that Terrapin doing
open Oh No did he get it while I was
looking away oh okay
what's wrong Beach you were crying out
for my help in your Sleet will you
having a nightmare
oh yes Bart levy I'm sorry for waking
you it was it was just so scary I felt
so alone without you by my side well you
don't have to worry about a thing I'm
here to protect you after all I will
always be there to protect my boy oh
yeah there was this utter dream to one
that didn't scare me
but angered me more than anything some
dumb [ __ ] on YouTube tried to
impersonate Tamers12345
one-two-three-four-five with a shitty
Sonic Underground fan animation like he
legit thought that he could become
popular by ripping off the greatness
that is Tamers12345 one two three four five
how could someone be so disrespectful
and uncreative it's just so [ __ ] sad
it's almost laughable
well he sounds like quit the loser with
no life unlike you who have the best
life because you have someone like me as
your lover someone who loves you with
older non-literary
and go back to bed before I get too
tempted and bang that cute little out of
your
how's he doing
George Bush well he's alive but that's
about it so he's still not talking
oh my he's persistent you would think
after six months of constant beatings
and torture he would talk by now five am
shining Spartacus
now are you going to tell us what we
want to hear today why are we going to
have to resort to some darker measures
and to getting you to talk
it'll do t-man t-man you don't even know
what you want with me I'll advise you
now it would be wise for you not elitist
today we are really on the edge ah yo
can supervise bish inlet alguien so get
burped in me ah smooches do Leakey
you little [ __ ] us we'll be next if you
don't watch your [ __ ] mouth white boy
wipe that smug look off your face before
I wipe it off for George that's enough
Goddamn it that's enough you're going to
kill it good let me kill him he's
getting on my last nerve
he's really tickled me [ __ ] us George
calm down let me take over from here
I'll go get the laptop laptop yes flat
top we've uncovered some info that we
believe will get you to tell us what we
want to hear what we want to hear about
the prophecy the prophecy that you don't
want us to know anything about
you won't go in we've been doing
research day and night and discovered
something interesting something
astonishing please take a look at this
chambers one two three four five YouTube
page
yeah it's socially what that you see
over the past four years Tamers12345 one two
three four five himself had been
dropping hints about the prophecy there
is going to be a huge war in the future
and he's getting ready you can't find
these and he left him videos he made in
the past starting all the way back in
the year 2013 it's quite incredible if
you ask me his plan this first back in
September 13th of 2013 we have the lazy
Underground opening video that was the
first time the prophecy was mentioned
and it was by you of all people
Sportacus you told Sonic and Bart will
be a prophecy that said the two of them
would fight in a Great War
then just a month later on October 1st
2013 we get another clue
in the video Darth Vader fights Luke in
the name of su Luke a division that told
of the same or
one year later on March 16 2014 the
prophecy was brought up again by you
Sportacus entertainers one two three
four five birthday bash video
you can be seen speaking with rb1 Kaname
someone who also seems to know about the
prophecy
then jumping ahead to August 26 2016 we
get mentioned of the prophecy again in
the Manic X min GA MV would matter
Mindi's dad claims to have a dream where
his determined he dies in a Great War
there is no doubt in my mind that he had
a dream about the prophecy it's
incredible isn't it Hamer's one two
three four five has been planning
something for nearly five years and
despite his YouTube channel being so
[ __ ] popular not a single person ever
picked up on it being able to keep all
this hidden chambers one two three four
five truly is an amazing man
I agree hey Alma Guerrero same intro
cientos Cuarenta Y Cinco is animus in
man boo do you Ron
Troy sunny Candela grown fans to let ma
eres a dosimeter cientos Cuarenta Y
Cinco fastened no habitants
Yoho spin - no Babu Temba calcio not Roy
Sonic undergrown falsely Cuse
shut up you think we're not true Sonic
Underground fans [ __ ] you [ __ ] you in
the ass
we love s you if you wear yellow visu we
are you don't ease even if it'll be a
walk the profits what we do Domingo wit
that mean Olesky that is none of your
business
we're asking the questions here so now
that you know that we know the prophecy
will you tell us what we want to hear
there's no use in lying to us anymore
mine will only resort in more pain it E
is a jingle [ __ ] alright then if that's
how you be then so be it
let's see if you can't still hold your
tongue after six more months of constant
torture how do you camp you George Bush
make sure he suffers greatly